League of Women Voters mss., 1913-2014 LMC 2371
Lilly Library
- 2018 Additions
  - Publications
    - Monroe County Government Officials Lists, 2011-2015 (Box 59)
  - Resources
    - Counterbudget: A Blueprint for Changing National Priorities (National Urban Coalition), 1971 (Box 60)
    - Environmental Cancer: A Report to the Public (Texas Reports on Biology and Medicine), 1978 (Box 60)
    - Hate Crimes in Indiana: A Resource Manual, November 1998 (Box 60)
    - Innovations in American Government (Ford Foundation), 1997 (Box 60)
    - Legislation Enacted, 110th Indiana General Assembly, 1998 (Box 60)
    - Lake Monroe Master Plan, 2015 (Box 60)
    - Misplaced Blame: The Real Roots of Populations Growth, 1997 (Box 60)
    - Monroe County: Quality of Our Environment, 1991 (Box 60)
    - The People and the Power Game: Citizen's Guide, 1996 (Box 60)
    - Sustainable Communities: From Vision to Action (Lamont C. Hempel), 1998 (Box 60)
    - Sustainable Communities: Guide for Grassroots Activists (Marilyn Hempel, Population Coalition), 1998 (Box 60)
    - Takings Law in Plain English (Christopher Duerksen, American Resource Information Network), 1994 (Box 60)
  - Studies
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Agricultural Update Acronyms, Glossary and Resources, 2014 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Expert Working Group on Farm Subsidies (Indiana), 2013 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Foreign Aid, 2013 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Genetically Engineered Foods and Regulatory Recommendations, 2012 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Introduction to Agricultural Technology, 2013 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Leader's Guide and Overview, 2013-2014 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - LWVBMC Response, March 2014 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Overview of Agricultural Subsidy, Articles on Subsidies, 2014 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Overview of Key Agencies, 2013 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - School Lunch, 2013 (Box 60)
    - Agriculture Update (LWVUS) - Suggested Summer Readings, 2013 (Box 60)
    - All-Day Kindergarten (LWVIN), 1991-2007 (Box 60)
    - Amending the Constitution (LWVUS) - Consensus Response - LWVBMC, November 2015 (Box 60)
    - Amending the Constitution (LWVUS) - Readings, 1965-2015; (11 folders) (Box 60)
    - Amending the Constitution (LWVUS) - Study Guide, 2013 (Box 60)
    - Education Concurrence (LWVIN) - Study Group Meetings, 2015 (Box 60)
    - Illegal Amphetamine Use (LWVIN), 2006-2007 (Box 60)
    - Immigration (LWVUS) - Readings, 2007 (Box 60)
    - K-12 High Stakes Testing (LWVIN) - Consensus Questions and Study Materials, 2016 (Box 60)
    - K-12 High Stakes Testing (LWVIN) - Department of Education - Assessment Alternatives, 2016 (Box 60)
    - K-12 High Stakes Testing (LWVIN) - Readings, 2016; (6 folders) (Box 60)
    - K-12 High Stakes Testing (LWVIN) - State Board of Education - Role, 2016 (Box 60)
    - K-12 High Stakes Testing (LWVIN) - Study Meetings and Readings, October-December 2016 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Consensus Questions and Committee Papers, 2015 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Consensus Response - LWVBMC, January 2016 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Discussion - Google Groups, 2015 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Introductory Materials, 2015 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - "Money in Politics: Developing a Common Understanding of the Issues", 2014 (Box 60)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - "Money in Politics: Who Owns Democracy?" (National Issues Forum), 2001 (Box 61)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Public Campaign Financing 101, 2015 (Box 61)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Readings, 2014-2015; (4 folders) (Box 61)
    - Money in Politics Review (LWVUS) - Study Guide, 2015 (Box 61)
    - Trade Policy update (LWVUS), 2001-2002 (Box 61)
    - United Nations (LWVUS), 1976 (Box 61)
  - Topics
    - Agriculture - Indiana, 1983-1999 (Box 61)
    - Bloomington - City Funding, 2015 (Box 61)
    - City-County Cooperation, 2005-2007 (Box 61)
    - City Government - Boards and Commissions, 1966 (Box 61)
    - City Government - Boards and Commissions - Appointing Authority, 2017 (Box 61)
    - Civic Health - Indiana Civic Health Index, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Community Development, 2001 (Box 61)
    - County Government, 1977 (Box 61)
    - County Government - School Reorganization Committee, 1964 (Box 61)
    - County Government - Urbanizing Area Plan, 2017 (Box 61)
    - Death Penalty, 2004-2006 (Box 61)
    - Education - Common-Core Curriculum, 2013 (Box 61)
    - Forests - Classified Forests Newsletters, 1989-1992 (Box 61)
    - General Assistance, Welfare, 1993 (Box 61)
    - Health, 2001-2004 (Box 61)
    - Health - Monroe County Health Department Annual Report, 2006 (Box 61)
    - Health Care - LWVUS Publications, 1993-2000 (Box 61)
    - Health Care - Medicare - LWVUS Publications, 1998-1999 (Box 61)
    - Health Care Costs, 1993-2002 (Box 61)
    - Health Care Reform Educational Kit, 2009 (Box 61)
    - Homelessness, 2014 (Box 61)
    - International Relations, 1998-2003 (Box 61)
    - International Relations - LWVUS Publications, 1983-1988 (Box 61)
    - International Relations - United Nations, 2002-2003 (Box 61)
    - Judicial Independence (LWVUS Project), 2000-2003 (Box 61)
    - K-12 Schools - Charter Schools, 2016 (Box 61)
    - K-12 Schools - Charter Schools - Indiana Charter School Board, 2015 (Box 61)
    - K-12 Schools - Vouchers, 2016 (Box 61)
    - K-12 Schools - Vouchers - Indiana, 2016 (Box 61)
    - Lake Monroe - Land Usability Study - SPEA Computer Program User's Manual, January 1976 (Box 61)
    - Land Use - Monroe County, 1976 (Box 61)
    - Local Government Reform, 2007 (Box 61)
    - Miller-Showers Park, 2002-2007 (Box 61)
    - Monroe County Boards and Commissions - Ordinance Revision, 2016 (Box 61)
    - MCCSC School Attendance Districts, 2005 (Box 61)
    - Natural Resources - Air Quality, 2001-2003 (Box 61)
    - Natural Resources - Bloomington Environmental Quality Indicators, 1997 (Box 61)
    - Natural Resources - Forests, 1996-2000 (Box 61)
    - Natural Resources - Lake Monroe Water Use, 2006 (Box 61)
    - Natural Resources - Land Use, 2006 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources - PCB Sites, 1993-2000 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources - Pesticides, 1989 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources - Recycling, 1991-2002 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources - Water Quality, 1992-2002 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources - Water Quality - LWVUS Publications, 1986-1998 (Box 62)
    - Peaker Power Plant, 2005 (Box 62)
    - Population, 1991 (Box 62)
    - Privatization, 2001-2002 (Box 62)
    - Public Access Laws (Indiana) - Handbook, 2012 (Box 62)
    - Putters Park, Ellettsville, 1994 (Box 62)
    - School Disciplines - Zero Tolerance, 2006 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Civil Rights, Civil Liberties, 1985-2004 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - "The Common Good: Social Welfare and the American Future", 1989 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Domestic Violence, 2001-2002 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Entitlement Funding, 1986 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Housing, 2000-2002 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Housing - Seniors, 2001 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Juvenile Justice, 2005-2007 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Midwest Partners (TANF), 2001-2002 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Poverty, 1987-1996 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Reproductive Rights, 1982-2003 (Box 62)
    - Social Policy - Women's Rights, 1984-2001 (Box 62)
    - State Agencies, 2006 (Box 62)
    - State Legislature, 1980-2007 (Box 62)
    - Taxation, 2005 (Box 62)
    - Taxation - Joseph Stiglitz, "Reforming Taxation to Promote Growth and Equity", 2014 (Box 62)
    - Taxes, 1985-2010 (Box 62)
    - TIF Districts, 2015 (Box 62)
    - Township Government, 1994 (Box 62)
    - Township Government - Accounting Uniform Compliance Guidelines Manual for Townships, 1999 (Box 62)
    - Township Government - Bloomington Township Assistance, 2002-2004 (Box 62)
    - Township Government - Indiana Township Trustees' Manual, 1993 (Box 62)
    - Township Government - State Board of Accounts - Bloomington Township, 1999-2006 (Box 62)
    - Utilities, 2001-2003 (Box 62)
    - Utilities (CBU) Review, 2006 (Box 62)
    - Voter Status Counts, 2016 (Box 62)
    - Voting Precincts - Monroe County, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Voting Rights Act, 2015 (Box 62)
    - Voting Statistics - Indiana, 2008-2014 (Box 62)
    - Water Pollution - Monroe County, 2004 (Box 62)
    - Water Quality - Fluoride, 1986 (Box 62)
  - Voter Services
    - Activities Summary, 1995-2016 (Box 62)
    - Appreciation Dinner, 2010 (Box 62)
    - Appreciation Event, 15 November 2012 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forum Information - "Empty Chair" Policy, 2008 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forum Information - Guidelines (LWVUS): Face to Face, 2007 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forum Information - Procedures and Timing, 1995-1998 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 1998 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2000 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2002 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2004 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2006 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2007 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2008 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2010 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2012 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Correspondence - Candidates, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Moderators and Panelists, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Planning Documents, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Scripts, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Venues, 2014 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - Bloomington, 28-29 September 2015 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums, 2016 (Box 62)
    - Candidate Forums - 9th Congressional District (not held), 2016 (Box 62)
    - Chair's Notes, 2007 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes, 2008 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes, 2010 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes - Presentation (Liz Feitl), 2010 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Emails, April-October 2015 (Box 63)
    - Chair's Notes (Diane Legomsky), January-April 2016 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 7 May 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 21 May 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 3 June 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 24 June 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 8 July 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 22 July 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 5 August 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 2 September 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 7 October 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, 28 October-December 2015 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, January 2016 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, February-April 2016 (Box 63)
    - Committee Meeting, July-December 2016 (Box 63)
    - Election Calendars, 2014-2016 (Box 63)
    - Election Legislation Summary, 2015 (Box 63)
    - Election Night Reporting, 1992-1995 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, 1985 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, 2000 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, 2002 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, April 2007 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, October 2007 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, April 2008 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, October 2008 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, April 2010 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, September 2010 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, March 2011 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, September 2011 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, April 2012 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, September 2012 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election, October 2014 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - General Election - Responses, October 2014 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates - Primary, April 2015 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, April 2015 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, October 2015 (Box 63)
    - Keys to the Candidates, October 2016 (Box 63)
    - Legislative Updates, 1997-2001 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Updates, 2007 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Updates, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Updates, 2016 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Updates, 2017 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Updates, 2018 (Box 64)
    - Materials Funding, 2015 (Box 64)
    - New Voter Discussion (Monroe County Youth Council, Josephine McCormick), 2016 (Box 64)
    - Official Materials, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Officials List - Correspondence, 1999-2013 (Box 64)
    - Officials List, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Officials List - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Officials List - Distribution, 2012 (Box 64)
    - Officials Lists - Other Leagues, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Poll Workers, 2002 (Box 64)
    - Service Agency Voting Information Project, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Education - Latino Community, October 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter Education - What Do County Commissioners Do?, 13 September 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter ID, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Lists and Information - Election Central, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration, 1995-2001 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration, 2007 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration, 2008 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration, 2012 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Farmers' Market, 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - High School Project, September-October 2012 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - High Schools, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - High Schools, undated (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Indiana University, 2012-2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Ivy Tech, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Kroger College Mall, 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Master Forms, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - MCCSC Open Houses, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Monroe County Public Library, 2012 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Monroe County Public Library, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Neighborhood Associations, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Resources (LWVUS), 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Seniors, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Senior Centers, 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Social Service Agencies, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration - Spanish-Speakers, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration Drives - Monroe County Guide, 2014 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration Handbook and Law, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration Training, August-September 2016 (Box 64)
    - Voter Registration Training, 2017 (Box 64)
    - Voting Machines, 2007-2009 (Box 64)
    - Voting Status Presentation, "To Enfranchise, or Disenfranchise, That is the Question", 2012 (Box 64)
  - LWV-IN
    - Anniversary Celebration, 1995 (Box 64)
    - Anniversary Celebration, 2010 (Box 64)
    - Anniversary Celebration, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Bylaws, 2003 (Box 64)
    - Campaign Finance Reform Project, 1999 (Box 64)
    - Coalition Statement, 1983-1988 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 64)
    - Education Fund, 2009 (Box 64)
    - Education Review and Study Group, 2015-2017 (Box 64)
    - Election Administration Materials, 2001 (Box 64)
    - Fact Sheets - Local Government Financing, 1984 (Box 64)
    - Fact Sheets - Presidency, 1977 (Box 64)
    - Fact Sheets - Welfare, 1976 (Box 64)
    - History, Policies, etc., 1985-1995 (Box 64)
    - Issue Advocacy, 2016-2017 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Action Network (LAN), 2007 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Link, 1992-1996 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Priorities, 1999 (Box 64)
    - Local League Liaison Policy, 2006 (Box 64)
    - Newsletters: The Voter, 1993-2012 (Box 64)
    - Poll Worker Survey, 2006 (Box 64)
    - Poll Worker Study - LWVBMC Response, 2006 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 19 February 2000 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day and Correspondence, 2002 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 6 March 2004 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 26 February 2005 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 11 February 2006 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 10 February 2007 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 9 February 2008 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 20 February 2010 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 19 February 2011 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 15 February 2014 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day (cancelled due to weather), 21 February 2015 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 22 February 2016 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 18 February 2017 (Box 64)
    - Presidents' Day, 17 February 2018 (Box 64)
    - Program: From Study to Action, 1995-1997 (Box 65)
    - Program: From Study to Action, 1999-2001 (Box 65)
    - Program: From Study to Action, 2006 (Box 65)
    - Redistricting Reform, 2011-2012 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Land Use Consortium, 2001 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2001 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2002 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2003 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2004 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2005 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, 2014 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Meetings, May-November 2017 (Box 65)
    - State Board - Reports, 1996-2007 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 19-20 May 1995 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 16-18 May 1997 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 6 June 1999 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 18-20 May 2001 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 16-18 May 2003 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 20-22 May 2005 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 27-29 April 2007 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 15-17 May 2009 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 27-28 April 2013 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, April 17-19 2015 (Box 65)
    - State Convention, 29-30 April 2017 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 13-14 May 1994 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 27 April 1996 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 28-29 April 2000 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 17-18 May 2002 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 14-15 May 2004 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 31 March-1 April 2006 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 25-26 April 2008 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 30 April-1 May 2010 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 31 May-1 June 2014 (Box 65)
    - State Council, 9 April 2016 (Box 65)
    - Statewide Studies and Positions, 2007 (Box 65)
    - Study - Energy Policy, 2001 (Box 65)
    - Study - Hazardous Waste, 2009 (Box 65)
    - Study - Healthcare, 1988 (Box 65)
    - Study - Juvenile Justice, 1976 (Box 65)
    - Study - Juvenile Justice Concurrence, 2006 (Box 65)
    - Study - Local Government, 2008 (Box 65)
    - Study - Poll Workers, 1999 (Box 65)
    - Study - Urban Crisis, 1978-1979 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Every Member Workshop, 5 October 1996 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Fall Workshop, 21 October 2000 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Fall Workshop, 20 October 2001 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Every Member Workshop, 2 November 2002 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Every Member Workshop, 23 October 2004 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Every Member Workshop, 29 October 2005 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Every Member Workshop, 21 October 2006 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Fall Regional Workshop, 23 August 2008 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Fall Regional Workshop, 14 August 2010 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Fall Regional Workshop, August-September 2012 (Box 65)
    - Workshops: Regional Workshop, July 2017 (Box 65)
  - LWV-US
    - Campaign Finance Reform: Strategies for Success in the Midwest - Destination Democracy, 1997 (Box 65)
      Includes 2 VHS tapes
    - Campaign Finance Reform: Strategies for Success in the Midwest - Readings, 1995-1997 (Box 65)
    - Campaign Finance Reform: Strategies for Success in the Midwest - Readings - Brennan Center for Justice, 1997 (Box 65)
    - Choosing the President, 1976 (Box 65)
    - Forum: Next Steps in Election Reform, Chantilly, VA, March-July 2005 (Box 65)
    - Get Out the Vote (GOTV), 1996 (Box 65)
    - History and Core Values, 2017 (Box 65)
    - Leader's Update, 2007-2009 (Box 66)
    - LWVUS Information, 1980-1994 (Box 66)
    - Membership and Leadership Development Handbook, 2013 (Box 66)
    - National Convention, Minneapolis, 10-13 June 2006 (Box 66)
    - National Convention, Portland, OR, 13-17 June 2008 (Box 66)
    - National Convention, Atlanta, 11-15 June 2010 (Box 66)
    - National Convention, Dallas, 6-10 June 2014 (Box 66)
    - National Convention - Notes (Above-Ground Storage Tanks, Healthcare, Human Trafficking), 2014 (Box 66)
    - National Convention - Notes (Advocacy, Fundraising, Leadership, Online Communications), 2014 (Box 66)
    - National Convention - Notes (Voter Registration Resources), 2014 (Box 66)
    - National Council - Revitalizing the League, 2017 (Box 66)
    - National Voter, 2000 (Box 66)
    - National Voter, 2001-2002 (Box 66)
    - National Voter, 2003-2004 (Box 66)
    - National Voter, 2005-2006 (Box 66)
    - National Voter, 2007-2009 (Box 66)
    - Natural Resources, 2012 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2000-2002 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2004-2006 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2008-2010 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2010-2012 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2012-2014 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2014-2016 (Box 66)
    - Positions: Impact on Issues, 2016-2018 (Box 66)
    - Resource Committee - Role, 1976 (Box 66)
    - Study - The Role of the Federal Government in Education (Proposed), 2009 (Box 66)
    - Vote 411.org, 2015 (Box 66)
  - LWV-US - Publications
    - Absentee Voting and Voter Registration...by State, 1978-1984 (Box 66)
    - Anniversary Membership Campaign Kit, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Choosing the President, 1976 (Box 66)
    - Citizens Building Communities: The ABCs of Public Dialogue, 2005 (Box 66)
    - Empowering Citizens: A Guide to Influencing Public Policy, 1996 (Box 66)
    - Energy Options, 1977 (Box 66)
    - Face to Face: A Guide to Candidate Debates, 1996 (Box 66)
    - The Federalist Papers Reexamined (Parts 2-6), 1977 (Box 66)
    - Indian Country, 1976 (Box 66)
    - LWV Diversity Tool Kit, 1999 (Box 66)
    - Making a Difference: A Voters Service/Citizen Information Handbook, 1978 (Box 66)
    - The National Voter Registration Act: Implementation Status Report, 1994 (Box 66)
    - Presidential Election Inequality: The Electoral College in the 21st Century (Fair Vote), 2006 (Box 66)
    - Protect Your Groundwater: Educating for Action, 1994 (Box 66)
    - Strategies for Effective Involvement: Drinking Water Source Assessment and Protection, 1998 (Box 66)
    - Supercity/Hometown USA: Prospects for Two-Tier Government, 1974 (Box 66)
    - Transforming Medicaid, 1996 (Box 66)
    - Transporting Radioctive Spent Fuel, 1996 (Box 66)
    - Understanding Economic Policy: A Citizen's Handbook, 1990 (Box 66)
    - Wired for Democracy: Using Emerging Technology to Educate Voters, 1995 (Box 66)